He did come back around a year later and be like, hey, so I wanted to apologize.
I was really being mean to you because I was intimidated by your intellect.
It was like, I felt like I was in competition with you.
Mind you, I'm over here just like, I just want you to love me.
I just want you to kick push to my heart.
Oh my God, Amanda, I've been through the same thing with a guy who like,
I felt this sense of, I always needed his validation.
I eventually cut him off because I felt like this is going nowhere.
And then years later, he came and apologized.
Very similar to Lupe's tone where it's like, I realized that I was intimidated by you.
I was in competition with you.
And it's like, have you noticed that when a man comes across a woman who he knows is a star,
his immediate instinct is to compete rather than to contribute to that light.
I don't understand.
Well, we do understand.
It's patriarchy.
There is.
We solved it. Episode over.
Is orange.
So if you had a question.
We solved it.
It was about 2 to 10 days later.
It was about...
It wasn't about 2 to 10 days ago or behold.
Does that mean we were algorith when a man leads to this?
We were sorted by.
And so we didn't leave the soundtrack.
We solved it.
Just do research this way.
I realised it when you were stuck at a recreation moment.
I took the народ where theRiona caught up and knew how to prepare yourself.